Guide to the Leadership Initiative Program records, 2003-2008.
Leadership Initiative Program records
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Leadership Initiative Program records, 2003-2008.
23-11-3767
NewYork State College of Human Ecology.Leadership Initiative Program.
1.3 cubic feet.
Manuscripts, Printed Materials, Research Materials
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Student portfolios done as final projects for several College of Human Ecology leadership courses taught by Brenda Bricker; includes course syllabi.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
A certificate program that encourages entrepreneurial and collaborative attitudes and actions to benefit students' personal development.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Student portfolios done as final projects for several College of Human Ecology leadership courses taught by Brenda Bricker; includes course syllabi.
SUBJECTS
Names:
NewYork State College of Human Ecology.; Bricker, Brenda; Cornell University--Students.; Cornell University.New York State College of Human Ecology.
Subjects:
Leadership.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Marissa Evans - HE 201, 2003 (Box 1)
- Team Project - HE 201 - "Fostering Leadership in Youth", Fall 2004 (Box 1)
- Samantha Acunto - "Mentoring in Leadership" - HE 406, Fall 2004 (Box 1)
- Rebecca Lee - HE 301, Fall 2005 (Box 1)
- Cara Santillo - Leadership Project Summary, 2006 (Box 1)
- Team Project - "Enviromaniacs Portfolio", Fall 2006 (Box 1)
- Team Project - "PITCH - Promoting Integration Through Community Hands", 2006 (Box 1)
- Dana Sckolnick - Leadership Project Summary, 2007 (Box 1)
- Grace Yi - "A Semester Long Search for the Leader Within", Fall 2007 (Box 1)
- Linda Willett - HE 301, Fall 2007 (Box 1)
- Team Project - "Financially Fit" (CD), Fall 2007 (Box 1)
- Team Project - "Empowering Change and Improving Global Health", Fall 2008 (Box 1)
- Team Project - "R.E.A.L. - Responsible Economic Action Leaders", Fall 2008 (Box 1)
- Rebecca A. Lee - "The Beginnings of a Pan-Asian Student Center at Cornell University" (CD), Fall 2008 (Box 1)
- Tracey Pacheco (CD), Undated (Box 1)
- Team Project - "S.M.I.L.E.Y. - Service and Mentorship: Inspiring Leadership, and Educating Youth", 2006 (Box 1)
- Camila Marquez - HE 405 - Mentoring in Leadership, Spring 2008 (Box 1)
- Human Ecology Research Association Forums, 2006, 2008 (Box 1)
- Leadership Initiative Program - Syllabi, History, 2003-2009 (Box 1)
- Jenna Marshall - HE 301 - "Collaborative Leadership", Fall 2005 (Box 2)